Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 1: Building Project Records, 1879-2002 July 2; 91 boxes
  - Woodrow Wilson School, 1961-1967; 3 boxes
    - Change Proposals, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Tests, 1963 October 3-1964 April 1; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Dining Room, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Field Directories, 1964; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Keys, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Landscaping, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Library, 1964; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Maintenance, 1964; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Move, 1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Operations, 1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Progress Reports, 1963; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Progress Schedules, 1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Punch List, 1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Magie Apartments, 1963-1969; 1 box
    - Ballard Todd - Correspondence, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Rheinstein Construction Company - Agreement/Payments, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - (Junior Faculty Housing), 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Change Orders, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Junior Faculty Apartments, 1959-1965; 1 box
    - Subcontractors, 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - David M. Todd, 1959-1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Ryan Construction Company - Correspondence, 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Releases and Waivers - General and Subcontractors, 1962 November 7; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Ryan J. W. and Company Incorporated - Contract Payments, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Magie Apartments, 1963-1973; 1 box
    - Insurance, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Progress Schedules, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Punch Lists, 1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Subcontractors, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Bids, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Change Orders, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Change Proposals, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Testing - Certified Testing Laboratories - Paid Invoices, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Testing - Certified Testing Laboratories - Reports, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Plans and Specifications, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1964-1973; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Junior Faculty Apartments - Job Meetings at Site, 1960 May 26-1961 September 13; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Computer Center, 1964-1972; 2 boxes
    - Correspondence from Architects, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Space Planning, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Space Planning #2, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence to Architects, 1965-1968; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Meeting Memos, 1965-1968; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Bids, 1968; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Transmittals, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Zoning, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Purchase Orders, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - (6920), 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - (6920), 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - (6920), 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Boxes, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Grant - National Science Foundation Correspondence, 1967-1972; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Grant, 1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - National Science Foundation Reports, 1971; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Math-Physics Basement, 1968; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Bidders, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Jadwin Gymnasium, 1963-1969; 1 box
    - Space Planning #2, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Space Planning #3, 1963-1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Space Planning, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Change Orders, 1966-1968; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Change Orders, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Change Orders, 1967; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Cage - Auditorium, 1964-1970 February; 2 boxes
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Plans, Specifications, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Joints Architectural Newsletter: The Cage, 1969 August; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Requisitions, 1965 November-1970 February; 2 boxes
      - No. 31, 1968 April-May; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - No. 32, 1968 May; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - No. 33, 1968 June-July; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - No. 34, 1968 July; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - No. 35, 1968 July-August; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - No. 36, 1968 August-September; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - No. 37, 1968 October-November; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - No. 38, 1968 November; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - No. 39, 1968 November-December; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 29)
      - No. 40, 1969 January; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 30)
      - No. 41, 1969 January-February; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - No. 42, 1969 February-March; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - No. 43-44, 1969 April-May; 2 folders (Box 60, Folder 33-34)
      - No. 45, 1969 June; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - No. 46, 1969 July; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - No. 47, 1969 August; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - No. 48, 1969 September-October; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - No. 49, 1969 October-November; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - No. 50, 1969 November-1970 February; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - No. 1, 1965 November; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - No. 2, 1965 December; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - No. 3, 1966 January 18; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - No. 5, 1966 March 10; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - No. 6, 1966 April 11; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - No. 7, 1966 May 10; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - No. 8, 1966 June 15; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - No. 9, 1966 July 12; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - No. 10, 1966 August 8; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - No. 11, 1966 September 12; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - No. 12, 1966 October 10; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - No. 13, 1966 November 10; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - No. 14, 1966 November-December; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - No. 15, 1967 January 5; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - No. 16, 1967 February 6; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - No. 17, 1967 February-March; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - No. 18, 1967 March-April; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - No. 19, 1967 April-May; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - No. 20, 1967 May-June; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - No. 21, 1967 June-July; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - No. 22, 1967 July-August; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - No. 23, 1967 August-September; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - No. 24, 1967 September-October; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - No. 25, 1967 October-November; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - No. 26, 1967 November-December; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - No. 27, 1967 December-1968 January; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - No. 28, 1968 January-February; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - No. 29, 1968 February-March; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 28)
      - No. 30, 1968 March-April; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Woodrow Wilson School - Minutes of Meetings, 1962 May 3-1965 October; 1 box
    - Woodrow Wilson School - Minutes of Meetings, 1964 January-1965 January; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Woodrow Wilson School - Minutes of Meetings, 1962 May 3-1963 December 27; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Woodrow Wilson School - Minutes of Meetings, 1964 January-July; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Woodrow Wilson School - Minutes of Meetings, 1964 August-1965 October; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - McCormick Hall, 1958-1966; 1 box
    - Meeting Minutes, 1959 April-1966 April; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - #4, 1966 January-December; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Addition (#3), 1965 January-June; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - #2, 1965 July-December; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Additions (#1), 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Testing - Paid Invoices, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Punch Lists, 1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Open Change Proposals, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Time and Materials Records, 1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Cases, Etc, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Art and Architecture Department, 1959-1966; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Fall Out, 1963; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Furniture, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Grounds and Buildings Department, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Insurance, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Marquand Library, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Mosaic File, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Mr. Orr, 1958-1962; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Plans and Specifications, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Progress Photographs, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Progress Schedule, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Punch Lists, 1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Subcontractors, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Alterations - Change Orders, #1-50, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Minutes of Meetings - Math-Physics Building, 1965 July-1966 November; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - McCormick Hall, 1958-1966; 1 box
    - Certified Testing Laboratories Reports, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Steinman, Cain and White, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - #15 - Changes, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Rheinstein Contract Payments, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Steinman and Cain, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Steinman, Cain and White - Agreement/Payments, 1958-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Bids, 1963; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1959-1965; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Additions, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Art Museum Equipment, 1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Math-Physics Building, 1963-1972; 3 boxes
    - (Miscellaneous), 1969; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Title I-II, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - National Science Foundation - Grant, 1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation - Reports, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Title I - Grant, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Title I - Proposal, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Title II - Grant, 1966-1971; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Physics Survey, 1968; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Budget, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Purchase Orders, Requisitions, Miscellaneous, Etc, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Purchase Orders, Requisitions, Invoices Etc, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Proposal - Office of Education, US Department of Health, Welfare and Education, 1963; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - National Science Foundation, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1972; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Physics - Used Furniture, 1968; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Physics Building - M. J. Doyle Incorporated, 1966-1968; 4 folders (Box 64, Folder 8-11)
    - Physics Building - Hugh Stubbins and Associates Incorporated, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 12-13)
    - Math-Physics Grants - Plans, Specifications, 1966; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Furniture, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Metal Stacks, 1969; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Lecture Hall Seating, 1968; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Math/Physics Library - Correspondence, Plans, Miscellaneous, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Furniture - Office Shelving, Desks, Tables, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Desk and Table Specifications, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Title II Proposal, 1965; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - National Science Foundation Correspondence, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - General, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Ambric Testing and Engineering Association Incorporated, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Report to National Science Foundation, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Test Reports - Physics Building, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Physics Building - Consolidated Incorporated, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Physics Complex - Ambric Testing - Structural Steel, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Physics Building - Ambric Testing - Folder #2, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Nassau Inn, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Nassau Inn - Accounts Receivable, 1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Nassau Inn - Improvements, 1978; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Pensions and Unions, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Colgate and Hanover Inns, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Residential Units, 1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Nassau Street East, 1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, 1978; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Stockholders, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Board Meeting, 1979 September 14; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Palmer Square - Board of Directors, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Board Meeting, 1979 June 15; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Finance Committee, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Report: Reuse of the Playhouse and Garden Theatres for Live Music, 1974 May 15; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Playhouse Theatre, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - E. A. Barton and Associates - Parking and Feasibility Study, 1977 September; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Palmer Square - Parking, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Fringe Parking, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Parking and Zoning, 1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1971-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Reports, 1979 January-May; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Haskins and Sells, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Laventhol and Horwath Reports, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Venturi and Ranch, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Venturi and Ranch, Other Borough Material, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Heating Vacuum and Air Conditioning Systems, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Budgets, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Expansion Schedules and Studies, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - General, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Citicorp Center, 1978; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - By-Laws, 1976; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Proposal - Use of University and Palmer Square Properties, 1977; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Consultants, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Cope, Linder and Walmsley, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Benson Building, 1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Central Business District, 1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated, 1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reviews, 1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated - Financial Statements, 1976 December-1977 December; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Palmer Square (Sweet), 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Financing, 1978; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Leases, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - English Shop (Option to Purchase English Shop Land), 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Griggs, Donaldson Properties, 1979; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Playhouse and Garden, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Sameric, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Management Proposals, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Cushman and Wakefield, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Feist and Feist, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Harold H. Goldberg and Company, Incorporated, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Helmsley-Spear, Incorporated (Hospitality Division), 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Hospitality Management Corporation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - M. A. Kravitz Company, Incorporated, 1974; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Mariner Enterprises, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - National Hotel Management, 1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Resorts Management, Incorporated, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Restaurant Associates, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 69, Folder 13-14)
  - Hotel Conference Center - Shopping Facilities, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Total Development Associates (Lease), 1978; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Deeds - Title Insurance Policies, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Elizabethtown Water Company, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Sewer Information, 1974; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Environment), 1973; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Sewer Information (2), 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Sewer #3, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Water - Wells, Etc, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Center Management Corporation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Square Management Corporation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Tishman East Management Corporation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Trusthouse Forte Incorporated, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Robert Warner, Incorporated, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Open Space Declaration, 1977; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Community Management Corporation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Housing, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Housing (#1), 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Sarshik and Edwards, 1976; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Sarshik and Edwards, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Conference Center #2, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Theobald Smith House, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Thomas A. Edison College, 1975; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Research Triangle Park, 1970-1978; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Hoffman-Rosner, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Verenigde Nederlandse Uitgeversbedrijven (Arete Publishing Company), 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Princeton Nurseries, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1977; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - St. Joseph's Seminary, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - RCA Corporation, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Tal-Star, 1979; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Town Personnel Agency, 1978; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Prudential, 1976; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Prudential, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Security, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Geology, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Drainage Permit (Department of Transport), 1969-1975; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Traffic Study - Sasaki, Dawson, Demay Associates, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Suburban Transit Corporation, 1976; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Application for Environmental Design Review, 1978; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly, 1978 April 24; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Publicity, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Talk to Class of 1951 - Princeton Forrestal Center, Princeton Club, 1977 March 22; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Meetings - Work Sheets, Etc, 1978; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Consultants, Meetings - Meetings with Governor Brendan Byrne, 1974 May 3; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate Committee (Internal), 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Meeting with Governor, 1978 March 24; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Meeting with New Jersey Officials, 1975 March 13; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Party, Football Game, 1979 September 29; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Golf/Tennis Outing, 1977; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Planning Data, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Princeton Bank and Trust, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - United Jersey Bank, circa 1975; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Hammer, Siler, George Associates Incorporated (Agreement), 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Sasaki, Dawson, Demay Associates - Agreement, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - K. S. Sweet Associates, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - K. S. Sweet Associates, 1976; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Princeton Forrestal Center - General, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Sweet - Budgets, Economics, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Accounting, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Princeton Forrestal Center - Reports, 1979; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - K. S. Sweet Associates - End of Year Report, 1979; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Advertising, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Cable Television, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Common Area Maintenance Charge, 1975; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Landscaping, 1977; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Personnel, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Population Density (Princeton Forrestal Center), 1976; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Air Charter Service (Ronson), 1978; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Oxirane International, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Prudential (#3), 1978; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Pru Research I and II, 1979; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - FMC Corporation, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - General Electric, 1977; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1976; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Mainstem Corporation, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Mobil, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Lewis C. Bowers and Sons Incorporated, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Lewis C. Bowers and Sons Incorporated, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 10)